Guide to the Thomas S. Foley Photographs 1905-1995
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Family and Political Photographs
  - Mrs. Reta Kahn of Bellingham, Washington, circa 1990-1994 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Washington State Delegation, circa 1990s (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Former Speaker Carl Albert, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Pea and Lentil Event, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Miscellaneous with President George H. W. Bush, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - CIA Cirector William Webster, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Representatives Rotenkowski, Hamilton, and Gillman circa 1990, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Mayor Al Halvorson and Others, Pullman, Washington, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Mike and Linda Geraghty, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Pondelay Paper, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Alfalfa Club New Members, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Unveiling of Bust of Kossuth, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Democratic Leadership and Ron Brown, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Heather Foley with Stevie Wonder, David Crosby, etc., circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - On a Sailboat with a Group, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Junior League, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Diane Hampton, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Phil Snowdow, Tom Tracy, Jay Pinnick-"Ag America", circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - William McCarter, Chairman of International Fund for Ireland, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Leadership Press Conference, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Hosting leadership lunch for Arafat, circa 1990s (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Gore, Hussein, Rubin at Joint Session, circa 1990s (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Press Conference, circa 1990s (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Pages and Interns, circa 1990s (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - 5th District School Visit to Capitol, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - "Face the Nation" with Newt Gingrich and Senator Nunn, circa 1990s (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Rotunda Ceremony Receiving the Cross of St. Andrew from Archbishop Iakovos, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Arnold Schwarzenegger, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Rabbi Kastenbaum, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Visiting Chaplain, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - NLEF Democratic Caucus Issues Conference, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Speaker's Press Conference with Hoyer, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - State of the Union Address with President George H. W. Bush, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Colville Tri-County Health District Representatives, circa 1990s (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - State Troopers, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - District Visit, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Radio-TV Correspondents' Association Dinner, with President George H. W. Bush, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - "Meet the Press", 1990 January 21 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Walla Walla, Washington City Managers, 1990 March (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - President George H. W. Bush, 1990 March (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers Reception with Stevie Wonder, Stephen Sondheim, Leonard Bernstein, 1990 May (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Pages and Interns, 1990 Summer (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Salk Jr. High, Spokane, Washington, Students, 1990 June (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Four Decades of American Military Heroism, 1990 June 7 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Quentin Perk, 1990 June 12 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Barley Growers of Washington, 1990 June 28 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Medal of Honor Ceremony, 1990 July (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Kevin Kline, Kathleen Turner, Morgan Freeman, Joseph Papp, 1990 July 12 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Gym Dinner with President George H. W. Bush, 1990 July 17 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Goodwill Games with President Ronald Reagan, 1990 July 19 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Magic Johnson, 1990 July 25 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Mitsubishi Corporation Members, 1990 August 27 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Joint Session of Congress with President George H. W. Bush, 1990 September 11 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - "Meet the Press" with Senator Bob Dole, 1990 September 16 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Maxine Waters and Les Aspin, 1990 September 26 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - "Meet the Press" with Secretary Nicholas Brady, 1990 October 7 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Gary Meyers, 1990 November (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - President George H. W. Bush, Michel, Mitchell, Dole in Saudi Arabia, 1990 November 21-22 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Pat Schroeder and Others on Christmas, 1990 December (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Tom Ward, 1990 December (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Y.M.C.A. Youth Governor's Conference, circa 1991 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Dedication of Boland Room, circa 1991 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - President George H. W. Bush, circa 1991 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Gonzaga University Representatives, circa 1991 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Girls Nation, circa 1991 (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Spokane, Washington Police, circa 1991 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - League of Women Voters, circa 1991 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Peggy and Terry Willcuts, circa 1991 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Pea and Lentil Event, circa 1991 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Kennedy Center Performance, circa 1991 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - EFS Group, circa 1991 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - President George H. W. Bush and Tip O'Neill, circa 1991 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - "Friends of Ireland" Gathering, circa 1991 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Representatives Gephardt and Michael, circa 1991 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Rosa Parks, circa 1991 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Heather Foley with Barbara Bush (signed), circa 1991 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - President George H. W. Bush, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - New York State Festival with Representative Rangel and General Colin Powell, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Address to Building Construction Trades Department, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Washington's Ancient Forests, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Civil Rights Passage Press Conference, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Joe T. San Agustin, Speaker of Guam Legislature, at Phillip Burton Memorial in San Francisco California, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Swearing-In, with Representatives Gingrich, Gephardt, etc., 1991 January (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Swearing-In of New Members, 1991 January (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Peng, 1991 January (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - State of the Union Address with President George H. W. Bush, 1991 January (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - President Roosevelt's Four Freedom Speech with President George H. W. Bush, Senator Dole, etc., 1991 January 30 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Persian Gulf-Desert Storm Joint Session, 1991 February (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Memorial Services for Silvio Conte, 1991 February (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Vice President Quayle on Air Force Two, 1991 February (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - National League of Cities Members, 1991 March (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Muhammad Ali, 1991 March (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Rosa Delauro and Lenders Bagel, 1991 March (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Joint Session of Congress with President George H. W. Bush and Heather Foley, 1991 March 6 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Dalai Lama, 1991 April 25 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Arnold Schwarzeneger, 1991 April 28 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - "Great American Workout" with Arnold Schwarzeneger, 1991 May (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Ted Danson, 1991 May 4 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - General Norman Schwartzkopf, 1991 May 8 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Private Sector Council Award Dinner, 1991 May 21 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Norton, Eleanor Hames, 1991 June (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Operation Civic Service, Robert Choate, 1991 June (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - President's Picnic and Congressional BBQ with President George H. W. Bush, 1991 June (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - William Baldwin and Elizabeth Shue, 1991 June (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - President George H. W. Bush in Cabinet Room at White House, 1991 June 11 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Representative Edward Madigan, 1991 July 18 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - President George H. W. Bush and Cabinet in Maine, 1991 August (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - "Meet the Press," with Senator Danforth, 1991 October 27 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Staff Accepting Award for Foley at "Hall of Honors", 1991 November (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Christmas Tree Lighting, 1991 December (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Staff, 1991 December (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Tae Kwon Do, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Ed and June Grey, Mary Sellecky, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - President Bill Clinton, circa 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous News Shows, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Harold Vaughn and Others, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - McFarland Jr. High School, Othello, Washington, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - UFCW - Bobby Brett and Larry Hall, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Beverly Boothroyd, Speaker of the House of Commons, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - President George H. W. Bush and Tip O'Neill, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - President Bill Clinton (then Governor) and Vice President Al Gore (then Senator), circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Dinner with President Bill Clinton (then Governor), Vice President Al Gore (then Senator), and Others, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Warren Beatty and Annette Benning, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Annette Booth of Senator Patty Murray's Staff, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Coin Striking with President George H. W. Bush, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - District Independent Insurance Agents, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Butch, Washington State University Mascot, and Tase T. Lentil, National Lentil Festival Mascot, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Boeing Corporation, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - D.J. and Company, Inc., circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Girls Nation, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - John Eisenhower, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - President George H. W. Bush, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - President Bill Clinton (then Governor), circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Vice President Al Gore (then Senator) on Capitol Hill, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Mack Hogans of Weyerhauser Company and Fred Benson, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Chris and Edward Victor, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - E.G. Marshall, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Dave Powers of Ketronic Company, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Hillary Clinton, 1992 February 18 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - House Leadership, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Miscellaneous photos with Senator Bob Dole and others, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Representative Bill Grey, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Campaigning for President Bill Clinton (then Governor) and Vice President Al Gore (then Senator), 1992 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Washington State Delegation, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Representative and Mrs. Robert Michel, Heather Foley, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Lincoln Middle School, Pullman, Washington, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Campaign Shots with Farmers, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - President George H. W. Bush, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - President George H. W. Bush and Representative Dick Gephardt, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - President George H. W. Bush at Radio-TV Dinner, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Heather Foley and Janet Kilpatrick, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Michael Schulof of Sony USA Inc., 1992 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - AIPAC Annual Policy Conference, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - House Gym Dinner with President George H. W. Bush, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - President George H. W. Bush at St. Patricks Day Party, 1992 March (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Holocaust Memorial Council Ceremony, 1992 April (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - President Bill Clinton (then Governor), 1992 April (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - American Ex Prisoners of War Event, 1992 April 9 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Arsenio Hall, 1992 April 9 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Honored by U.S. Committee of the International Institute, 1992 April 29 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Michel Portrait Unveiling with President George H. W. Bush, Bob Dole, and others, 1992 May 4 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Luciano Pavarotti, 1992 June (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Suffolk University Law School Commencement, 1992 June (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - In "The Chamber", 1992 June (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Vice President Al Gore (then Senator), 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Salk Middle School, Sacajawea Middle School, and Bowdish Jr. High, Spokane, Washington, 1992 Fall (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - "Tom Foley Appreciation Day", 1992 September 5 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Christmas Tree Lighting, 1992 December (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Weightlifting with Gregg and Joe, circa 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Jeff and Natalie Horner, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Rural Electric Company, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Jean Wells and Alice Stolz, League of Women Voters, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Billy Joel, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Launi Myley, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Mr. Hinkle, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Representative Leslie Byrne, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - President Bill Clinton, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Joe Tasker, Compaq, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Washington D.C. Staff, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Colville Tribal Council, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Pennsylvania Natural Resources, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Sharma Shields of Spokane, Washington, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - House Leadership Press Conference on Unemployment Compensation Bill, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Heather Foley with Tipper Gore, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Tom Ward Award Ceremony, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Pages Genevieve Ford, Marian Leonardo, Christopher Cohen, and Ann Guthmiller, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Representative Brewster, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Sine Die Conference, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Rob Leonard, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Vice President Al Gore and Representative Gephardt (signed), circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Representative Kweisi Mfume, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Pages and Interns, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - President Bill and Hillary Clinton (signed), 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Inauguration and Swearing-In Ceremony, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Presiding as Speaker, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - State of the Union Address with President Bill Clinton, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - President Bill and Hillary Clinton, Heather Foley (signed), 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Indian Carpet in Capitol Hill, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - "Race for the Cure" with Vice President Al Gore, Heather Foley, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - President Bill Clinton, Vice President Al Gore, Cabinet Members, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Vice President Al Gore, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - President Bill Clinton in Washington State, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - President Bill Clinton, Vice President Al Gore, Senator Mitchell, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Receiving Award from Flax Trust, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - NBC Inaugural Celebration with Tip O'Neill, 1993 January (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - "Meet the Press", 1993 January 10 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Walt Disney Representative Joe Shapiro, 1993 January 15 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Playfair with Heather Foley, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - President Bill Clinton on Inauguration Day, 1993 January 20 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Family Leave Bill Conference with President Bill Clinton, Vice President Al Gore, 1993 February (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Freshmen Lunch with Representative Brooks, 1993 February (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - President Bill Clinton at Podium, 1993 February (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Amy Marie Volt, Winner of Writing Award-Spokane Review, 1993 March (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - White House Leadership Meeting with President Bill Clinton, 1993 March (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Phillip Burton Memorial Celebration, 1993 March (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - President Bill Clinton at St. Patricks Day Party, 1993 March 17 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - AMA Members, 1993 April (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Steve Scardan, 1993 April (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - Heather Foley with Hillary Clinton at Congressional Spouse's Reception, 1993 April (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Heather Foley with Mr. and Mrs. Saari, 1993 April (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - UI Bill Signing with President Bill Clinton, 1993 April (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - American-Ireland Fund Dinner with President Bill Clinton, 1993 April (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - President Bill Clinton, Representative Dicks on Air Force One, 1993 April (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - President Bill Clinton, 1993 April (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - Foley at U.S. vs Russia Wrestling Event, 1993 April 10 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Collenade Hotel with Heather Foley, 1993 May (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Campaign Finance Proposal Announcement with President Bill Clinton, 1993 May (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Statue of Freedom Removal, 1993 May (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Heather Foley with President Bill Clinton at White House Dinner, 1993 May (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Motor Voter Bill Signing with President Bill Clinton, 1993 May (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - RCA President Ed Koschalk, 1993 June (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Heather Foley with Hillary Clinton at White House Barbeque (signed), 1993 June (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - President Bill Clinton and Vice President Al Gore, circa 1993 June (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Spring Pages, 1993 June (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - President George H. W. Bush, 1993 June (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - President Bill Clinton in Statuary Hall, 1993 July (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Hillary Clinton (signed), 1993 Summer (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - President Bill Clinton, Vice President Al Gore, Representative Gephardt, 1993 July 15 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - President Bill Clinton at Capitol, 1993 August (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Health Care Workshop with Hillary Clinton, 1993 September (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - "House on the Hill" in "Life" Magazine, 1993 September (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - National Service Bill Signing with President Bill Clinton (signed), 1993 September (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Joint Session Address on Health Care, 1993 September 22 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Heather Foley with President Bill and Hillary Clinton at Joint Session Address on Health Care, 1993 September 22 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Les Aspin's Retirement Dinner for General Colin Powell at Museum of American History, 1993 September 29 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Hiro Yamagata, 1993 October (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Governor Ann Richards of Texas, 1993 October (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - President Bill Clinton, 1993 October (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Statue Ceremony with President Bill Clinton, Vice President Al Gore, Heather Foley, etc., 1993 October 23 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - President Bill and Hillary Clinton Presenting Health Care Bill to Congress in Statuary Hall, 1993 October 26 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - President Bill Clinton, 1993 November (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Heather Foley with President Bill Clinton on Air Force One, 1993 November 18 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Heather Foley and President Bill Clinton, 1993 December (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Treasury Lloyd and Mrs. Bentson (signed), 1993 December (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Vice President Al and Tipper Gore, 1993 December (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Hillary Clinton (signed), 1993 December (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - President Bill and Hillary Clinton, Heather Foley in Formal Attire, 1993 December (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Christmas Tree Lighting, 1993 December (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - President Bill Clinton, 1993 December (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous Unknown People, circa 1994 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Groundbreaking Event, circa 1994 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Frank and Mrs. Yose, circa 1994 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Jim Connelly, circa 1994 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - President Bill Clinton in Informal Attire, circa 1994 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Representative Siskorski in Minnesota, circa 1994 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - President Bill Clinton and Vice President Al Gore at Capitol Hill, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Terry Mangan, Larry Erikson, Chuck Fulton, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Nancy Vanbest, Debbie O'Brien, Josh Frank, Ophelia Howley, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Building and Construction Trades Council of Spokane, Washington, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - President Bill Clinton and Representative Gephardt, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Issues Conference with President Bill Clinton, 1994 January (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - State of the Union Address with President Bill Clinton and Vice President Al Gore, 1994 January 25 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Alfalfa Club Dinner with President Bill Clinton and President George H. W. Bush, 1994 January 29 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Bill Signing with President Bill Clinton and Leadership, 1994 February (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - "Smoke Signals", 1994 February (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Bill Natcher Funeral with President Bill Clinton, 1994 February (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - President Bill Clinton (signed), 1994 February (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Florida Delegation at Florida State University Celebration in Statuary Hall, 1994 February (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Eastern Washington School Board Directors, 1994 February 8 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Ambassador Jean Kennedy Smith, 1994 March (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Machinist Union Craig McClure and Others, 1994 March (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Mary Ann McCurdy, 1994 March (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Washington State Farm Bureau Delegation, 1994 March 2 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Wellpinit High School Juniors (Wellpinit, Washington), 1994 March 9 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Annual Awards Dinner with Steven Seagal, 1994 March 15 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Phillip Church, David Hally (Local 712) and Rian Van Leuven (Local 608), 1994 March 16 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - St. Patrick's Day Party with President Bill Clinton and Vice President Al Gore, 1994 March 17 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Tanya Druffel of Colton High School (Colton, Washington), 1994 March 17 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Laura Rice of Republic High School (Republic, Washington), 1994 March 17 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Pages Kyle Snoudon and Mark Winter, 1994 Spring (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Memorial Tribute to Tip O'Neill, 1994 April (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Central Valley High School Members (Spokane Valley, Washington), 1994 April (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - President Richard Nixon's Funeral with Bob Hope, 1994 April 27 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Federated Women in Timber, 1994 May (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Representative Natcher's Funeral with Vice President Gore, Representative Michael, 1994 May 4 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Dedication of Jack Dean Legal Services Center with Justice Anderson, Judge Quackenbush, Paul Strimatter, 1994 May (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Democratic Caucus with President Bill Clinton, 1994 May 22 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Kevin Scrinner and Time Coleman, 1994 Summer (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Vice President Al Gore, 1994 June (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Bill Signing with President Bill Clinton, 1994 August (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - "Meet the Press", 1994 October 2 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Christmas Tree Lighting, 1994 December 14 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Tree Planting Ceremony with Heather Foley, 1994 December 22 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - "Meet the Press", 1994 December 25 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - House Minority Leader Robert Michel, circa 1994 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Addressing Speaker's Chair from Well, undated (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Campaign Address at Washington State University, undated (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Dole, Wright, undated (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Morris Dees of Southern Poverty Law Center, undated (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - National Environmental Development Association Dinner with Representatives Nelson and Regula, undated (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - "BF" and President of American Smelting Company, undated (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Heather Foley and Mac Hammond, undated (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - At a Reception, undated (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Max Baucus and Others Outside Foley's Home, undated (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Mo Cohen, undated (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Puget Sound Naval Base Association, undated (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Mike Lowrey and Mrs. Denny Miller, undated (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Charlie Melody and Robin Webb, undated (Box 6, Folder 90)